Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep within your
dreams Taking aim for your heart,
so it would seem Stand tall and read,
go to hell and jump for
paradise Every time dangerous,
dangerous We like it serious,
serious, oh Looking deep in the dream,
there is the one in pain Turns out that's
the one who means the most to you today
Adventure calls now,
let's go The balls filled between us, they
will show Still what we don't know Yes,
working hard together Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through believing in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers
All the love and the tears
in the world we're in
United gently bringing up our thought
again, yeah We're the foolish ones we love,
we'll carry on
Till we see the light, the sun will rise
The greatest fight at its core is
against myself forevermore Come on,
let's do it now,
let's go The bonds built between us,
they will show So what we don't know,
that's what we call adventure Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through believing in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers Superpowers
Yes, we've got superpowers
Superpowers Yes,
we've got superpowers
Superpowers Superpowers
32 minutes remaining
before Luffy's planned
rendezvous with his crew on Kaku Island.
No Straw Hat and no Katakuri either.
Guess their fight is really dragging out.
Maybe Straw Hat's tougher
than we thought he was?
Oh, come on!
What exactly are you trying to imply here?
That Straw Hat might win?
Because that's not happening!
And you get that through
your thick skull, Nuji!
What the hell?
What are you picking on me for?
I'm Nushi and I didn't say anything!
Katakuri doesn't lose!
That's his whole thing!
Get with the program, you dope! Huh?
Unlike you, Nuuji,
Katakori's the perfect man!
I'm not Nuuji!
Sorry about that, Nuuji, Nuu-san.
Why?!
You owe us one!
That's not how it works!
Still, something has to be going
on in there that bothers me.
Put yourself in Straw
Hat's shoes for a sec.
He's not supposed to rendezvous
with his crewmates until 1am.
In other words, even if he
wasn't expecting an ambush,
there's no point in coming early.
He can't win the fight,
but he can capture Barrel.
And she's the key to
the mirror world, right?
So he grabs her,
jumps through a mirror, and waits it
out on some island where it's safe.
Makes sense to me.
That explains why nobody's heard
from her in such a long time.
Good point.
Straw Hat is likely running for his life
right now, but that doesn't change much.
Because once 1 a .m.
hits, he'll be coming out of
this mirror one way or another.
So our plan still works.
Brulé's not too quick on the upticks,
but it's no surprise she'd get caught.
Akimek, stop.
If she's listening through a mirror
somewhere, you might make her cry.
Oh, see?
Still half an hour, but
let's try to stay sharp.
We don't mind if you
come early, Straw Hat.
My sickle can't wait to meet your neck.
They're armed, meaning they're
pirates, not civilians.
Must have broken all the other mirrors,
so Luffy has to come out of that one.
The second he shows, we're
going to have to haul ass.
Otherwise, we're both dead.
I'm going to be in a hurry, so we might
need to say our goodbyes soon, Pudding.
That okay?
Why are you all the way over there?
I happen to like it over here, that's all.
And for the record, I can
hear you perfectly fine.
Fudgy.
Dear.
Thinking back, it was pretty
funny how we met, huh?
This is your fiancé, Lili.
Lady Charlotte Pudding.
I want us to get married tomorrow.
I know we weren't together for
long, but I had a lot of fun.
I'll never forget you.
Thank you for everything.
How can you say that when I lied to you?
I tried to kill you.
How can you smile at me like that, Sanji?
I have to apologize while I still can.
This is it.
My last chance.
Shut the hell up, you idiot!
Oh, damn it!
Why do I keep doing that?
Well, I guess we're still enemies
at the end of the day, aren't we?
From your perspective, our marriage
was just a means to an end.
A trap staged from the start to the finish
with me walking straight
towards my own death.
Sorry.
I'm sure it must have
been an awful experience.
But there was nothing bad about it.
Because you were by my side.
Oh, uh, hey, I'm sorry.
I hope I didn't insult you or anything.
Stop it, you stupid dears!
Stop crying!
I didn't mean anything
bad by it, okay? Promise.
Please don't cry.
Hey, Sanji, dear.
Could you do me a favor?
One last thing, before you
go, stay right there, please.
Oh, my God.
Impressive efforts from the Straw Hats.
Just can't keep them down.
If they still managed to escape
despite your preparations,
that would indeed be frightfully big news.
Oh, I bet you'd like that.
But those fools haven't got a chance.
We had to swallow our pride,
but we're ready this time.
We dispatched a whole army to make sure
they never pull one over on us again.
So even if Gold Roger himself
pops out of that mirror somehow,
you better believe we'll
shut him down fast.
Once we're done with the Straw Hats,
will line their severed heads in a row
and you can put that on your front page?
sends a message, huh?
That's rather tasteless
not to mention unnecessary
I think it's just the
right amount of brutality.
It won't be long now, fellas.
We've got a whole fleet out there.
There's no way their ship
is making it through!
Come back!
Work over that cake right now!
The tail's on fire!
This is the end of the road, Lili.
She's got us.
We'll be long dead before
we make it to that island.
Let's trash the cake
and make a break for it.
You're going to lose your cool on me now?
Lili?
We all came from different
places, but we're together now.
So whether we live or die, let's do it.
There's a stinking family.
I think I see something
It's Fluffy Island
Let's give it one final push I
want to see some hustle, boys
Looks like we'll make it by 1am
like we promised at least i know
luffy can win a fight but i'm
a bit worried about him getting
out if he can't capture Barrel
and use her power again then he'll
be stuck in the mirror world
luffy is not the kind of person to
carefully calculate that sort of
thing is he unfortunately no then
we have to help him out what
should we do come to think of it i
don't know if we'll be able to
tell what time it is really well
there's a lot that could go wrong
but we still believe in you Luffy
Even when he falls, he
doesn't land on his back.
We're headed to Kaku Island right now.
But it's going to be at least
10 hours before we make it.
So around 1 a .m.
First things first, kick that guy's ass!
Then look for a mirror
that leads to Kaku Island?
And we'll meet you there, okay?
What time is it anyway?
Tell me one last thing
Will you return to defeat Big Mom someday?
I have to, don't I?
Cause I'm gonna be king
of the pirates Yes!
You're seeing quite far into the future.
Oh, my God.
Branch, let's go.
Hey, you here?
She's gone.
Oh, crap, I can't get
out of here without her.
What should I do?
There's no time left!
Katakuri!
How could he do this to you?
Rich!
It's Barrel, you rotten little imp!
I don't know what kind of dirty trick you
used to beat my brother, but shame on you!
So you brought down Katakuri, huh,
kid? Most impressive! Eat out!
Who are you?
Mysterious mistoes!
I've captured Barrel for you and have
been waiting here to aid in your escape!
Glad you made it out, okay.
Thanks, Peckle!
Here's the deal!
Pedro sacrificed his life to save you
and your crew so you can't die now!
Not on my watch!
Let's go, Straw Hat.
It's almost 1 a .m., and I'm sure
your friends are waiting for you.
I want no part of this.
Cacao Island, straight ahead.
That's a lot of ships.
A massive fleet indeed.
Hey, Sanji, how are
things looking over there?
Luffy's not here yet.
Don't get close to the shore.
I'll try to bring Luffy to the
ship without engaging the enemy.
The clock is ticking.
Are your weapons ready?
If Straw Hat is going to show,
then it'll be in five minutes.
Your funeral is waiting.
Only four minutes left.
Hmm.
No way.
I'm sure that's them.
It's the Straw Hat ship.
They're here!
I think they've spotted us!
It truly is an overwhelming number.
They can't take us all!
Set them on the spot!
They're coming!
Oh no!
We are gonna die!
Lupe, hurry!
Maintain our distance from the shore!
Seems wise to me.
Smoothie?
So what's our next move?
They're trapped.
We don't need to rush into this.
We'll simply support the
main force from the rear.
The Totoland Grand Fleet, led by
Snap, is immediately ahead of them.
With us to their rear, they don't
have an inch of wiggle room.
They're doomed even if they
do make it to the island.
Oven has a massive army ready
and waiting to kill them.
Whatever they do next is inconsequential.
This is the end of the line for them.
Keep all the transponder snails connected.
We need intel from every angle.
I want to give them a crushing defeat.
As you wish, sir, I'll keep you posted.
I hope you're saying your prayers, brat.
Stop making us wait.
Come out and fight!
Luffy, come on. Hurry.
Somebody. Anybody.
You gotta help me.
What's Sulong?
You don't know?
Get out.
It's a primal form.
When a mink stares at a full moon, then
they turn Sulong and wield incredible power.
Unfortunately, I'm not good at it.
I'll rather at controlling it.
The transforming part I can do just fine.
But I'll become nothing
more than a raging beast.
And then what? Mayhem.
I'll start running wild and
destroy everything around me.
Nobody can reach me once
I'm like that. Not anymore.
Because there's only one man
who could save me from myself.
And that's big bro Pedro!
Get out!
Pec-Holmes!
That's enough!
There was just something about
his voice that calmed me down.
He could always bring me back from the
edge before I completely lost myself.
Pedro.
No.
Whenever I transform, there won't be
anyone left who can reach me in that state.
Get up!
Listen, there's a full
moon tonight, Straw Hat.
So when I go through this mirror
to Kaku Island, I'll transform.
And then all bets are off!
When I'm going on a
rampage in my Sulong form,
that'll be your chance to
escape from Kaku Island.
You idiot.
That plan'll never work.
They'll butcher you.
Look, the force of Cacao Island is
big enough to launch a whole war.
Even if you transform, they'll cut you
down like the traitorous fool you are.
Don't drop me!
Cannon, we're not listening to you!
Straw Hat will be there in a second!
Don't you dare forget
what Pedro did for you.
You cannot let his
sacrifice be made! Get out!
Thanks, Peckums.
I promise.
Right.
Now it's your turn brewing.
Huh?
Here we go!
It's coming from inside the mirror.
Someone help me!
That totally sounds like Barrel,
as I thought she was captured
and used by Straw Hat.
He will pay.
He's coming aim and fire! Why?
That's strange.
My name's Miss Hampec Holmes.
You had better start talking or else.
Wait, get back!
Don't you dare move an inch—you try any
funny business and you'll regret it.
You hear me—this gun ain't no joy, don't
you think I will blow her brains out?
Get off!
Please put
the gun down—are you crazy?
Hey, Pecos, what are you trying to pull?
Let's calm down and talk this out.
What's wrong with you?
Let her go—don't kill me.
Have mercy!
kill me have mercy
This disguise was pointless, since they'd
know who I was as soon as I transformed.
No turning back now.
I will protect Straw Hat with
every last ounce of my strength,
because he is the man that Big
Brother Pedro put his life on!
You're kidding me!
Whoa, he's too long for him, huh?
Come on, Pestle, don't do it!
You're gonna flip out and
get all of us killed, man!
Get away from here!
Hold him back!
It's too late now.
Prepare yourselves!
Hey!
Cut it out!
What the hell?
I expected Straw Hat or at least
Katakuri to come out of the
mirror and instead I get to deal
with this deranged circus freak!
You have no right to
point a gun at my sister!
So put that damn thing down!
He got me!
It's...
Weeding!
Yay!
That was cool!
It's Straw Hat!
Luffy...
Please!
Better, better, better, better, better.
Click.
Can you hear me? Yes, Angie! Good news.
Luffy's here.
It's Straw Hat!
Petcombs was hiding him.
Let's get him!
He must have tricked Katakuri
and made a run for it.
Pretty impressive, actually.
Me first!
He's up there!
Straw Hat, why'd you jump?
You're an easy target, up here.
Just surrender!
Big Brother Raisin!
Who's helping out Straw Hat?
Sanchi!
Win your fight?
Uh-huh!
Heh, I knew he would.
They're trying to escape through the air!
That's Blackleg!
Foolish.
Easy to counter.
You think you're special?
We could use Gippo too, dummy! One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Make it so he'll never
see the full moon again.
Peckhams, no!
Are you ignoring me?
How rude!
Struggle as hard as you like.
No one can overcome this many foes.
Surely even you must realize it by now.
Damn it.
Hmm.
There's an explosion at the harbor!
Damn it! What now?
Well, what just happened to me?
The ships near the shore are all burning.
What happened?
Is this a bombing?
They've got an entire fleet
of snacks, sir! Who are they?
It seems to be...
Jerobo Double Six!
What the hell?
I thought we wiped them out!
Was that report a lie?
Next round!
Prepare to fire!
Jerobo Double Six!
Open fire!
German Devil Six.
You owe us after that tea party.
And you'll pay with interest.
Don't test your luck with me!
Did you come to help us?
Oh, Sanji, you're here.
We stopped by to crush these fools.
Can't let you have all the fun.